# Alex Gonzalez

# **Software Developer**

2066 Rush Bay Way Orlando, FL 32824

321-536-0497 me@alexg.dev alexgonzalez.dev

Skills

Javascript, jQuery, AngularJS, CSS/SCSS/HTML, Bootstrap, Responsive Design

Java, NodeJS/Express

SQL, MongoDB, JSON

Agile development/Scrum methodology utilizing Atlassian products

Objective

Motivated software developer with five years of experience utilizing front and back end tools. Quick-learning team player eager to learn new technologies and manage existing projects with a demonstrated ability to cooperate with a team to deliver results.

**Experience** 

## Katmai Government Services/ Software Developer

APRIL 2018 - PRESENT, ORLANDO FL

Collaborated in the creation of an online portal for the Navy with responsiveness and latency in mind. Integrated front and back end technologies using Liferay. Communicated with different teams, such as design, systems, and test, to ensure new and existing features had the same look-and-feel. Presented upcoming features to customers in live demonstrations.

#### **Newscycle Solutions / Software Developer**

MAY 2015 - APRIL 2018, MELBOURNE FL

Migrated an existing legacy product to a web client. Managed responsiveness, browser compatibility, localization, UI/UX, and external libraries of the entire project. Lead front end developer crucial in the development of web client.

**Education** 

### Florida Institute of Technology / B.S. in Computer Science

AUGUST 2012 - MAY 2015, MELBOURNE FL